?מאיפה נכנסנו...
.טוד
?בסדר, טוד
.תודות
.על לא דבר
אפשר לקבל
?כוס קטנה של יין לבן זול
.תודה
?פומפס
?מה התשובה
.אה, אנחנו לא הולכים למלון
.אנחנו הולכים הביתה
- ווטרס, אריק פלצ'ר -
- תאריך פגיעה 16/2/1944 -
- מקום הפגיעה: אפריליה, איטליה -
- קבורה: מונטה קסינו, איטליה -
- נסיבות המוות -
- נעדר בפעילות, נחשב למת -
- רוג'ר ווטרס החומה -
# So ya
# Thought ya
# Might like to go to the show
# To feel the warm thrill of confusion
# That space cadet glow
# Tell me is something
eluding you, sunshine?
# Is this not what you expected to see?
# If you wanna find out
what's behind these cold eyes
# You'll just have to
claw your way through this disguise #
!אורות
!הרץ אפקטים קוליים
!ו........אקשן
.שחרר את זה עליהם
# Momma loves her baby
# And daddy loves you too
# And the sea may look warm to you babe
# And the sky may look blue
# But Baby
# baby blue
# Oooooh babe
# If you should go skating
# On the thin ice of modern life
# Dragging behind you the silent reproach
# Of a million tear-stained eyes
# Don't be surprised
When a crack in the ice
# Appears under your feet
# You slip out of your depth
and out of your mind
# With your fear flowing out behind you
# As you claw the thin ice #
# Daddy's flown across the ocean
# Leaving just a memory
# A snapshot in the family album
# Daddy, what else did you leave for me?
# Daddy, what d'ya leave behind for me?
# All in all it was just a brick in the wall
# All in all it was all just bricks in the wall
YOU!
Yes, you!
Stand still, laddie!
# When we grew up and went to school
# There were certain teachers who would
# Hurt the children in any way they could
# By pouring their derision
# Upon anything we did
# And exposing every weakness
# However carefully hidden by the kids
# But in the town, it was well-known
# When they got home at night,
Their fat and
# Psychopathic wives would thrash them
# Within inches of their lives
# We don't need no education
# We don't need no thought control
# No dark sarcasm in the classroom
# Teachers leave them kids alone
# Hey! Teachers! Leave them kids alone!
# All in all it's just another brick in the wall
# All in all you're just
Another brick in the wall
# We don't need no education
# We don't need no thought control
# No dark sarcasm in the classroom
# Teachers leave them kids alone
# Hey! Teachers! Leave us kids alone!
# All in all you're just
Another brick in the wall
another brick in the wall #
Wrong! Do it again!
If you don't eat your meat,
you can't have any pudding!
How can you have any pudding
if you don't eat your meat?
You!
Yes! You behind the bikesheds.
Stand still, laddie!
# All in all it's just another brick in the wall
# All in all you're just
Another brick in the wall
# Just another blunder
# Just another lousy call
# Just another clap of thunder
# And apologies ring hollow
# From the guilty in Whitehall
# And there's no him' of sorrow
# In the whitewash on their walls
# And nothing is gained
# And Jean Charles de Menezes
# Remains
# Just another brick in the wall #
הייתי רוצה
להקדיש לו את הקונצרט הזה
מנדז, נהרג בידי שוטרים בריטים)
(חף מפשע בשל זהוי שגוי
ולכל קורבנות טרור המדינה האחרים
.בכל מקום, בכל רחבי העולם
כשהייתי צעיר
.ניגנו בלונדון
.צילמנו כמה הופעות שם
.יש לי סרט קצר כאן הערב
?וזה... אה
."קליפ בו אני שר את השיר "אמא...
אנסה לשיר קול שני
ולנגן בגיטרה אקוסטית
עם המסכן האומלל
הדפוק הקטן, רוג'ר
.מלפני שנים רבות
!30
!אחלו לנו בהצלחה
.תודה
- ארל קורט 1980 -
# Mother do you think
They'll drop the bomb?
They'll like this song?
# Mother do you think
they'll try to break my balls?
# Oooooohh ahhhh
# Mother should I build the wall?
# Mother should I run for president?
# Mother should I trust the government?
# Mama will they put me in the firing line?
# Oooooohh ahhhh
# Is it just a waste of time?
# Hush now baby, baby, don't you cry
# Mother's gonna make
all of your nightmares come true
# Mother's gonna put
All of her fears into you
# Mother's gonna keep you
right here under her wing
# She won't let you fly
but she might let you sing
# Mama's gonna keep baby
Cosy and warm
# Ooooh babe
# Oooooh babe
# Of course mama's gonna
Help build the wall
# Mama do you think she's good enough
# For me?
# Mama do you think she's dangerous
# To me?
# Mama will she tear your little boy apart?
# Mother will she break my heart?
# Hush now baby, baby don't you cry
# Mama's gonna check out
all your girlfriends for you
# Mama won't let anyone dirty get through
# Mama's gonna wait up until you get in
# Mama will always find out
where you've been
# Mama's gonna keep baby
Healthy and clean
# Ooooh babe
# You'll always be baby to me
# Mother, did it need to be so high? #
.תודה
אני מרגיש כאילו אנחנו נוסעים
.במעגלים במשך שעות
?זה הנוף, לא
.כן. זה הצרפתים, אני חושב
?איפה הייתי
אה, כן, יש את הסרט הזה
על נהג משאית רוסי
.והוא נשבר במונגוליה
יש את הסצנה הזאת
שבו הוא נהיה מאוד, מאוד שיכור
,והוא נושא נאום נלהב וארוך
על כך שהוא לא יכול
.להזכר בשמו של סבו
כשראיתי את זה
.הרגשתי כמו סכין בלב
".ואני, "הו, אלוהים
,חשבתי, "סבא שלי
מה לעזאזל
"?היה שמו של הסבא שלי
.ונבהלתי
,וכמה שניות לאחר מכן
,דרך הפאניקה
."אמרתי, "ג'ורג' הנרי
.הוא נהרג כאן בשנת 1916
כלומר, זה בלתי אפשרי לדמיין
.איך זה באמת היה
שחור משחור, מפחיד כאופל
הבחורים בתעלות
הבחינו די מהר
שלמקבלי ההחלטות
לא היה זין של מושג
.מה לעזאזל הם עושים
.ברור שלא
,כל העניין היה מטורף
,כך היה מההתחלה
והמשיך להיות מטורף
עד הסוף כשהם נסוגו
.והלכו הביתה
ובן כמה היה אביך
?כשאביו נהרג
.בן שנתיים
אז זה שתי מלחמות שלקחו
אפילו את הזיכרון הישיר
.של אבות משני בנים
.כן
,רוב השליטים משקרים
אך שקרים כבר פחות מזעזעים
פחות מקוממים
מהבורות המטופחת מבחירה
.ששבלייה מתיחס אליה כאן
בורות זו מכחישה את המציאות
.של כל דבר שמעורר חמלה
,טעות לחשוב על מנהיגי מלחמה כאלה
,או, על אסטרטגים כלכליים של היום
.כעל חסרי חמלה
.הם אובייקט
זה מה שאנחנו צריכים ללמוד
.ולפעול לפיו
.הם אובייקט
.ג'ורג' הנרי, כורה פחם
זאת היתה שאיפה שלי
.לבוא לכאן עם שלושתכם
.שני נינים, נינה ונכד
.זה שני מיליון אנשים. מדהים
אתה יכול לתכנן
.לפגוש אנשים בחלומות שלך
?אתה יכול
.כן -
,ובכן, כשאתה הולך לישון הלילה
אני רוצה שתתכנן להיפגש
.עם ג'ורג' הנרי בחלומותיך
פעם חלמתי
,שקפצתי במורד גבעה
.אבל אני נחתתי ליד דוב והוא אכל אותי
יכול להיות שיש לך
.חרדות מרוסים
.או רק כללית מדובים
.גם זה אפשרי
אף פעם לא הייתי בשליטתה על חלום
.שבו אמרתי, "אה, אני חולם
עכשיו אני יכול לעשות
. את זה, או את זה, או משהו אחר
זה קרה לי פעם אחת
,ואז איבדתי שליטה
והותקפתי על ידי חיילים
.יפנים ממלחמת העולם השניה
?הותקפת על ידי חיילים יפניים
.כן
## Look, Mummy.
There's an aeroplane up in the sky.
# Did, did, did, did you see
the frightened ones?
# Did, did, did, did you hear
the falling bombs?
# Did, did, did, did you ever wonder why
we had to run for shelter
# When the promise of a brave new world
unfurled beneath a clear blue sky?
# Did, did, did, did you see
the frightened ones?
# Did, did, did, did you hear
the falling bombs?
# The flames are all long gone
but the pain lingers on
# Goodbye, blue sky
# Goodbye
# Goodbye #
# What shall
# We use
# To fill
# The empty
# Spaces
# Where waves
# Of hunger
# Gnaw?
# Shall we set out
# Across this sea of faces
# In search of more
# And more applause? #
# Shall we buy a new guitar?
# Shall we drive a more powerful car?
# Shall we work straight through
The night?
# Shall we get into fights?
# Leave the lights on? Drop bombs?
?זה האם סיורים במזרח
# Contract diseases?
# Bury bones? Break up homes?
# Send flowers by phone?
# Take to drink? Go to shrinks?
# Give up meat? Rarely sleep?
# Keep people as pets?
# Train dogs? Raise rats?
# Fill the attic with cash?
# Bury treasure? Store up leisure?
# But never relax at all
# With our backs to the wall #
# Backs to the wall...
# I am just a new boy
# Stranger in this town
# Where are all the good times?
# Who's gonna show
This stranger around?
# O I need a dirty woman
# O I need a dirty girl
# Will some woman in this desert land
# Make me feel like a real man?
# Take this rock and roll refugee
#  babe, set me free
# O I need a dirty woman
# O I need a dirty girl
# O I need a dirty girl #
,באשר למשרתת שלה
היא יכולה לסעוד
.עם עובדי המטבח
.טוב מאוד, אדוני
רק תודיע לי
.ברגע שאתה יכול
# Day after day, love turns grey
# Like the skin of a dying man
# Night after night, we pretend it's all right
# But I have grown older
# And you have grown colder
# And nothing is very much fun any more
# And I can feel
# One of my turns coming on
# I feel
# Cold as a razor blade
# Tight as a tourniquet
# Dry as a funeral drum
# Run to the bedroom
# In the suitcase on the left
# You'll find my favourite axe
# Don't look so frightened
# This is just a passing phase
# One of my bad days
# Would you like to watch TV?
# Or get between the sheets?
# Or contemplate the silent freeway?
# Would you like something to eat?
# Would you like to learn to fly?
# Would you like to see me try?
# Would you like to call the cops?
# Do you think it's time I stopped?
# Why are you running away? #
# O babe
# Don't leave me now
# Don't say it's the end of the road
# Remember the flowers I sent
# I need you, babe
# To put through the shredder
in front of my friends
it O babe
# Don't leave me now
# How could you go?
# When you know how I need you
# Need you, need you, need you
# To beat to a pulp on a Saturday night
it O babe
# Don't leave me now
# How can you treat me this way?
# Running away
#  babe
# Why are you running away?
?ווטרס: איפה אנחנו
.צרפת
?ווטרס: ואנא מועדות פנינו
.לאיטליה
.ווטרס: אכן זה נכון
.נצטרך לעבור דרך מנהרות
.איש: כך אני מקווה
ווטרס: זוכר את הפעם האחרונה
?שעברנו דרך מנהרות
.היינו בטח בני 17 או 18
.היינו בדרכנו לבגדד
.איש: לא, זאת היתה איסטנבול
?באמת
.אבל עברנו דרך יוון
.וטפסנו על האולימפוס
ווטרס: אתה זוכר
?שהותקפת על ידי כלב
.לא
?זוכר סערה
.לא, לא זוכר
.אז אנחנו בסדר
.הזיכרון האנושי הוא מכשיר מטעה
.במיוחד בגיל שלנו
זה לא משהו שיש לתת לו
.יותר מדי תשומת לב
רוצה לשמוע את הסיפור על
?סופת הרעמים שאתה לא זוכר
.כן בבקשה
.בסדר -
...אז, אנחנו הולכים ככה
.והיה רעם
הקול והאור
.הגיעו בו זמנית
,ובאותו רגע
איבדתי את זהותי לגמרי
.למשך כשנייה אחת
,ובשנייה הזאת
.ידעתי שאני בלתי מוגבל
.הייתי על פסגת ההר ההוא
לא יותר רחוק ממך
.מאשר המכונית הזאת
.לגמרי
.ואני לא זוכר שום ברק -
.לא
אז אתה רומז שזה
.אולי לא קרה בכלל
!?... אני לא
כלומר, ובכן, כן. אני רומז
.וודאי אני רומז
,אבל מצד שני
זה יכול היה לקרות בקלות
.ואני פשוט לא זוכר את זה
.בסדר
.אולי נפגעתי מברק -
...פעם היה לי את החלום הזה
והחלום היה
,שרצחתי מישהו
.והרגשתי אשמה שלא תאומן
לבסוף, יום אחד, הבנתי
.שחשבתי שהרגתי את אבי
.והחלום לא חזר שוב
הילד שבתוכי, שלקח אחריות
,לכל מה שקרה סביבי
.נשאתי את זה עד אמצע החיים
,אני לא צריך יותר את החלום ההוא
.והוא לא חזר
.אכן
.ודאי שלא הייתי נזכר בזה
,ובכן, כל מה שאומר
מאחר והדבר היחיד שהזכרתי
הוא שזאוס חושף
...את חוסר הגבולות שלי
.אכן
...הייתי בניו יורק...
,כי הבן השני של ננסי היה שם
,ואני מחזיק אותו ככה
.והוא מסתכל עלי, והוא מחייך
וכמובן, אנחנו מתוכנתים
,להגיב לחיוך הזה
.והוא מתוכנת  לחייך אותו
.אבל זה לא מה שחשבתי
,מה שחשבתי היה
האור שבא ממנו
והאיר את הכל
היה זהה למה שקרה לי
כשהייתי בן 18
.וזאוס ברך אותי בברק
.אבל זה כל מה שיש
.זה רק זה
,חיוכו של הנכד
.וברכתו של המלך האלים
.והם אותו דבר
.אני יכול להגיד לך את זה
רוג'ר, יקירי, האם אי פעם סיפרתי לך
?את סיפור הבריחה שלי מבודפשט
.פעם או פעמיים
...כוח ביטחון לאומי אזרחי
#I don't need no arms around me
# And I don't need no drugs to calm me
# I have seen the writing on the wall
# Don't think I need anything at all
# No! Don't think I'll need anything at all
# All in all it was all just bricks in the wall
# All in all you were all
Just bricks in the wall #
# Goodbye, cruel world
# I'm leaving you today
# Goodbye
# Goodbye, all you people
# There is nothing that you can say
# To make me change my mind
# Goodbye #
.לחיים
.תודה
.פרנסואה
.כנראה לא משנה הרבה
.לא אשאר הרבה
אני עוצר רק למשקה
.כי, אני בדרכי לאיטליה
,אני יודע שאתה לא מבין
.וזה בסדר
,אז, הייתי רוצה עוד אחד לדרך
.ואז אני יוצא מכאן
.תודה
.אז הם נחתו בסלרנו
,דרך המגף האיטלקי
.עד שהגיעו למונטה קסינו
.ושם, הם עצרו
,אלה היו הגרמנים
,על ראש הגבעה, ככה
.והנהר היה כאן
אז הם החליטו
שהם ישאירו אנשים כאן
,והם פנו לכיוון הים
,והלכו דרך כאן
.ושאפו ליצור ראש-גשר כאן
.דרומית לרומא
.באנציו
.וכך עשו, בינואר 1944
,ואבא שלי נכנס
והם תיגברו את
.ראש-הגשר באנציו
.ופשטו עליהם
.אז הבחור הזה מת
.ולכן אני הולך לאנציו
כי אף פעם לא ראיתי את הגלעד
.לאבא שלי, אריק
.אז, זה הסיפור
,אני יודע שאתה לא מבין
.אבל נראה לי שאקח עוד אחד, לדרך
רוג'ר היקר, אני לא חושב
שאי פעם סיפרתי לך על
.שתי הבריחות שלי מהונגריה
,הראשונה ב 1944
.מהכיבוש הגרמני
.הייתי בן שבע
הבניין שלנו היה מוקף
.על ידי האס-אס ההונגרי
,אכלנו ארוחת צהריים
,והמשרתת הביאה את המרק
,והיא פתאום התחילה לצעוק
,אתה חייב לבוא מייד לראות"
כי לוקחים את
.כל היהודים מחוץ לבניין
ואבי אמר, "חייבים לעזוב
".עכשיו, בלי כלום
.וקמנו, ועזבנו את הדירה
,ואיך שירדנו
,ראיתי אדם רץ על חייו
ואחרי שתי שניות, שני אס-אס הונגרים
.רצים אחריו עם אקדחים שלופים
,אבי אמר "מה שלא תעשה
,"אל תסתכל
,ופתח את דלת הכניסה
.ובשנייה הזאת שמעתי את היריות
,ואנחנו ברחוב
,ואני פוחד להסתכל, אבל אני מסתכל
ושם ראיתי את
.הגופה הראשונה בחיי
עברנו ליד הגופה הזאת
אל פינת הרחוב
.והצלחנו לחמוק מעיניהם
,התחבאנו, עד סוף המלחמה
.בשכנות לגסטפו
,בסוף המלחמה הסתיימה
לא באופן דרמטי
.וחזרנו לבודפשט
,וכשנכנסנו לדירה
על השולחן בחדר האוכל
היו ארבע צלחות המרק
.אתה יודע, עדיין עם המרק, יבש, בתוכן
וכמו ילד, לא יכולתי להאמין
איך המקום הזה שרד
כל ההרס שקרה
,באירופה ובעולם
.אבל ארבע הצלחות נותרו ללא פגע
,כך עמדתי ובהיתי בשולחן
לא מבין איך הזמן
.עמד מלכת במקום הזה
# Hey, you, out there in the cold
# Getting lonely, getting old
# Can you feel me?
# Hey, you, standing in the aisles
# With itchy feet and fading smiles
# Can you feel me?
# Hey, you, don't help them
To bury the light
# Don't give in without a fight
# Hey, you, out there on your own
# Sitting naked by the phone
# Would you touch me?
# Hey, you, with your ear against the wall
# Waiting for someone to call out
# Would you touch me?
# Hey, you, would you help me
to carry the stone?
# Open your heart, I'm coming home
# But it was only fantasy
# The wall was too high
# As you can see
# No matter how he tried
# He could not break free
# And the worms ate into his brain
# Hey, you, out there on the road
# Always doing what you're told
# Can you help me?
# Hey, you, out there beyond the wall
# Breaking bottles in the hall
# Can you help me?
# Hey, you, don't tell me
There's no hope at all
# Together we stand, divided we fall
# We fall, we fall, we fall... #
.נותרה לנו שעה של אור יום
.עדיף שנתחיל
?זה בטוח לנוע בלילה
.זה יהיה הרבה פחות בטוח להישאר כאן
.אביך יעלה על עקבותינו די מהר
?לורקה יכול לרכוב
.כן, אני יכול לרכוב
.לורקה, הגיע זמן ללכת
.תודה לך על הכל
# ls there anybody out there?
# ls there anybody out there? #
# I've got a little black book
With my poems in
it Got a bag with a toothbrush
And a comb in
# When I'm a good dog,
they sometimes throw me a bone in
# I got elastic bands keepin' my shoes on
# Got them swollen hand blues
# I got thirteen channels of shit
on the TV to choose from
# I've got electric light
# And I've got second sight
# Got amazing powers of observation
# And that is how I know
# When I try to get through
# On the telephone to you
# There 'll be nobody home
# I've got the obligatory Hendrix perm
# And the inevitable pinhole burns
# All down the front
Of my favourite satin shirt
# I've got nicotine stains on my fingers
# I've got a silver spoon on a chain
# I've got a grand piano
to prop up my mortal remains
# I've got wild staring eyes
# And I've got a strong urge to fly
# But I got nowhere to fly to
it O babe
# When I pick up the phone
WOMAN". (ON PHONE}
Surprise, surprise, surprise!
# There's still nobody home
# I've got a pair of Gohills boots
# And I got fading roots #
Where the hell are you, Simon?
מה שמדאיג אותי
...הוא הצד האחר שלו
...שבא בצרוף לדוגמה
,המתורגם לפעולה פוליטית
.אשר הורגת אנשים
...וזה
.ובכן, בזה אני איתך, חבר -
בסיור
אני מזמין כ20 ותיקים פצועים
.למופע כל לילה
.היה בחור אחד
,והוא רק הנהן
,ואז הוא הושיט את ידו
ואני תפסתי ביד שלו ככה
,ללחוץ את ידו
.והוא לא עזב לי את היד
אז חשבתי, "אוקיי, הוא ללא ספק
".רוצה לומר משהו
והוא עמד שם
.והביט בי ישר בעיניים
.מאוד מוזר, מבט חודר
...ואז הוא אמר
.אבא שלך היה גאה בך
.וזה היה רגע מאוד מוזר
...אני רק
,אני פשוט הפכתי לג'לי, באמת
.והרגשתי שמשהו גואה בי
.לעולם לא אשכח אותו
# Does anybody here
Remember Vera Lynn?
# Remember how she said that
# We would meet again some sunny day?
# Vera!
# What has become of you?
# Does anybody else in here
# Feel the way I do? #
# Bring the boys back home
# Don't leave the children
on their own, no, no
# Bring the boys back home
# Don't leave the children
on their own, no, no
# Bring the boys back home #
# Hello?
# ls there anybody in there?
# Just nod if you can hear me
# ls there anyone at home?
# Come on, now,
I hear you're feeling down
# Well I can ease the pain
# Get you on your feet again
# Relax. I'll need some information first
# Just the basic facts
# Can you show me where it hurts?
# There is no pain you are receding
# A distant ship, smoke on the horizon
# You are only coming through in waves
# Your lips move
but I can't hear what you're saying
# When I was a child I had a fever
# My hands felt just like two balloons
# Now I've got that feeling once again
#1 can't explain you would not understand
# This is not how I am
#1
# Have become comfortably numb
# O.K. Just a little pinprick
# There 'll be no more aaaaaaaaah!
# But you may feel a little sick
# Can you stand up?
#1 do believe it's working, good
# That'll keep you going through the show
# Come on it's time to go
# There is no pain you are receding
# A distant ship, smoke on the horizon
# You are only coming through in waves
# Your lips move
but I can't hear what you're saying
# When I was a child
I caught a fleeting glimpse
# Out of the corner of my eye
#1 turned to look but it was gone
# I cannot put my finger on it now
# The child is grown
# The dream is gone
#But I
# Have become comfortably numb #
#Ahh...
# O Ma,  Pa
# Must the show go on?
# O Ma
# Take me home,
Take me home, take me home
# O Pa
# Let me go, let me go, let me go
# Do I have to stand up
# Wild eyed in the spot light
# What a nightmare
# Why don't I turn and run?
# Turn and run
# O Ma
# Take me home,
Take me home, take me home
# O Pa
# Let me go, let me go, let me go
# It was just a mistake
# I didn't mean to let them
take away my soul
it Am I too old, is it too late?
It O Ma, O Pa
# Where has the feeling gone?
# Will I remember the song?
It O ooh, ooh
# The show must go on #
#80 ya
# Thought ya
# Might like to
# Go to the show
# To feel that warm thrill of confusion
# That space cadet glow
# I've got some bad news
For you sunshine
# Pink isn't well,
He stayed back at the hotel
# And they sent us along
As a surrogate band
# We're gonna find out
where you fans really stand
# Are there any queers
In the theatre tonight?
# Get them up against the wall!
# There's one in the spotlight,
he don't look right to me
# Get him up against the wall!
# That one looks Jewish!
# And that one's a coon!
# Who let all of this riff-raff into the room?
# There's one smoking a joint
# And that one's got spots!
# If I had my way, I'd have all of you shot!
# You!
# It only takes one of them all
# And you! #
Are there any paranoids...
in the stadium tonight?
This is for you!
It's called Run Like Hell!
We shall clap.
Louder!
Follow me!
That's better. Altogether now!
Enjoy yourselves!
# Run, Run, Run, Run
# Run, Run, Run, Run...
# You better make your face up in
your favourite disguise
# With your button down lips
and your roller blind eyes
# With your empty smile
# And your hungry heart
# Feel the bile rising from your guilty past
# With your nerves in tatters
it As the cockleshell shatters
# And the hammers batter
# Down your door
# You better run
# Run, Run, Run, Run
# Run, Run, Run, Run...
# You better run all day
# And run all night
# And keep your dirty feelings
# Deep inside
# And if you're taking your girlfriend
out tonight
# You'd better park the car
well out of sight
# Cause if they catch you in the back seat
trying to pick her locks
# They're gonna send you back to mother
in a cardboard box
# You better run #
it Eins, zwei, drei, alle!
# Ahh, Ahh...
# O you cannot reach me now
# No matter how you try
# Goodbye, cruel world, it's over
# Walk on by
# Sitting in a bunker
# Here behind my wall
# Waiting for the worms to come
it Worms to come
# In perfect isolation
# Here behind my wall
# Waiting for the worms to come
it Worms to come
We're waiting
to succeed and going to convene
outside Brixton Town Hall
where we're going to be...
# Waiting
# To cutout the deadwood
# To clean up the city
# Waiting
# To follow the worms
# To put on a black shirt
# Waiting
# To weed out the weaklings
# To smash in their windows
and kick in their doors
# Waiting
# For the final solution
to strengthen the strain
# Waiting
# To follow the worms
# To turn on the showers
And fire the ovens
# Waiting
# For the queens and the coons
and the reds and the Jews
# Waiting
# To follow the worms
# Would you like to see
# Britannia rule again
# My friend?
# All you have to do is follow the worms
it Would you like to send
our coloured cousins
# Home again, my friend?
# All you need to do is follow the worms #
We'll be moving along
at about 12 o'clock down Stockwell Road.
...12 minutes to 3:00
we'll be moving along
Lambeth Road towards Vauxhall Bridge.
Now when we get to
the other side of Vauxhall Bridge,
we're in Westminster Borough area.
It's quite possible
we may encounter some...
...by the way we do
# Stop!
# I wanna go home
# Take off this uniform
# And leave the show
# And I'm waiting in this cell
# Because I have to know
# Have I been guilty all this time? #
# Good morning, Worm your honour
# The crown will plainly show
# The prisoner who now
Stands before you
# Was caught red-handed
Showing feelings
# Showing feelings
of an almost human nature
# This will not do
# Call the schoolmaster!
#1 always said he'd come to no good
# In the end your honour
# If they'd let me have my way
I could have flayed him into shape
# But my hands were tied
# The bleeding hearts and artists
# Let him get away with murder
# Let me hammer him today?
# Crazy
# Toys in the attic I am crazy
# Truly gone fishing
# They must have taken
My marbles away
# Crazy
# Toys in the attic he is crazy
it Call the defendant's wife!
# You little shit you're in it now
# I hope they throw away the key
# You should have talked with me
more often than you did
# But no!
# You had to go
# Your own way, have you broken any
# Homes up lately?
# Just five minutes, Worm your honour
it Him and Me, alone
# Baaaaaaaaaabe!
# Come to mother baby,
let me hold you In my arms
# M'lud I never wanted him to
# Get in any trouble
# Why'd he ever have to leave me?
It Worm, your honour,
Let me take him home
# Crazy
# Over the rainbow, I am crazy
# Bars in the window
# There must have been a door
there in the wall
# When I came in
# Crazy
# Over the rainbow, he is crazy
# The evidence before the court is
# lncontrivertab/e
# There's no need for the jury to retire
it In all my years of judging
I have never heard before
# Of someone more deserving
# Of the full penalty of law
# The way you made them suffer
# Your exquisite wife and mother
# Fills me with the urge to defecate!
# Since, my friend,
you have revealed your deepest fear
#1 sentence you to be exposed
before your peers
# Tear down the wall!
# Tear down the wall! #
it All alone, or in two's
# The ones who really love you
# Walk up and down outside the wall
# Some hand in hand
# And some gathered together in bands
# The bleeding hearts and artists
# Make their stand
# And when they've given you their all
# Some stagger and fall,
After all it's not easy
# Banging your heart against some
# Mad bugger's wall
זאת תודה גדולה
.מגראהם ברואד
- גראהם ברואד, תופים -
- ג'ון קארין, קלידים -
- הארי ווטרס, אורגן ופסנתר -
- ג'ה סמית, גיטרה ובאס -
- רובי ווייקאפ, קולות -
- קיפ לנון, קולות רקע -
- מארקי לנון, קולות רקע -
- פאט לנון, קולות רקע -
- ג'ון ג'ויס, קולות רקע -
- סנוואי וייט, גיטרה -
- דייויד קילמינסטר, גיטרה -
.(וממני, תודה רבה (ספרדית
.תודה
!תודה
...זה לא
- רוג'ר ווטרס החומה -
- מוקדש לכל אהובינו הנופלים -
אפר ויהלומים, אויב ואוהב"
".כולנו שווים בסוף